borderfree.com 2015-12-04

# Privacy Policy | Borderfree

**Last Updated:** June 19, 2015

This Privacy Policy is for Borderfree, Inc. (f/k/a FiftyOne, Inc. dba FiftyOne Global Ecommerce) and its subsidiaries, including BoxHop LLC (for the purposes of this Policy, collectively "Borderfree"). Borderfree understands how important your privacy is to you. Rest assured that your privacy and trust are also very important to us.

This privacy policy details the personal information we collect about you, the means through which we collect that information, with whom we share it and how you can change your preferences regarding how we collect and use your information when you provide it to us at sites within the following domains (“Borderfree Websites”): [borderfree.com](http://www.borderfree.com/), [boxhop.com](http://www.boxhop.com/), [port51.com](http://www.port51.com/), and [fiftyone.com](http://www.fiftyone.com/) and BY VISITING BORDERFREE, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE PRACTICES DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

  * What Types of Personal Information Does Borderfree Collect?
  * What Cookies and Other Technologies Does Borderfree Use?
  * How Does Borderfree Use and Share Your Information?
  * How Does Borderfree Handle, Store and Secure Your Information?
  * How Can You Make Choices About Receiving Marketing, Promotional and Other Information?
  * What Should You Understand About Third-Party Advertisers and Links to Other Websites?
  * Are Children Allowed to Use Borderfree?
  * Do We Conduct Questionnaires, Panels, Contests, or Sweepstakes?
  * Has a Third Party Reviewed This Privacy Policy?
  * Is Borderfree Both EU & Swiss Safe Harbor Compliant?
  * What Should I Know About Changes to This Privacy Policy?
  * What are the Terms & Conditions and Dispute Resolution?

#### What Types of Personal Information Does Borderfree Collect?

We collect, store, and use information that you provide directly to us and information we acquire in other ways, each as detailed immediately below.

  * Information We Acquire From You Directly. We acquire information from you when you (a) provide information via any of the Borderfree Websites, including any user accounts or other accounts, (b) interact with any of Borderfree’s checkouts, (c) participate in any Borderfree questionnaires, panels, contests, or sweepstakes, (d) communicate or interact with Borderfree customer service (via email, mail, courier, fax, web form, and/or phone) and/or (e) engage in any other electronic or oral conversation with an employee, contractor or agent of Borderfree. Through these channels, you might provide us with information about you, information about the recipient of any merchandise you are ordering and/or having shipped, including, in either case, names, email addresses, postal addresses, phone numbers, genders, birthdays, marketing preferences, personal interests, credit card information, and other financial information, including driver's license numbers, CPF numbers, and passport information.
  * Information We Acquire in Other Ways. We also acquire other information about you when you interact with the Borderfree Websites and certain of their features, including user accounts and other accounts, checkouts, questionnaires, panels, contests, sweepstakes and social media features ("Social Media Features"), such as signing into a Borderfree Website account using your social media sign-in credentials or otherwise interacting with third party social media features that are enabled on the Borderfree Websites. This information may be collected by us or our third party partners through log files and may include your city and country location, your IP address, your browser, mobile device or other device, a unique identifier for your browser or device and details of your usage such as your preferences, “pins”, “likes” and “dislikes”. Another example would include confirmations that we receive when you open an email from us or our partners, if your computer or other device supports that function. We may also acquire information about you from our subsidiary companies, business partners, other third parties and publicly available information and combine that information (or compare that information) with the information otherwise detailed throughout this privacy policy.
  * Blogs. Certain of our blogs may be managed by third parties using third party applications and you may be required to register with such third party applications in order to post a comment. We may not have access or control of the information posted to the blog. In such cases, you will need to contact or login to the third party application if you want the personal information that was posted to the comments section removed. To learn how the third party uses your information, please review the third party’s privacy policy.
  * Testimonials. With your consent, we may display your testimonial along with your name on the Borderfree Websites.  If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at optout@borderfree.com.

#### What Cookies and Other Technologies Does Borderfree Use?

A cookie is a small file downloaded on to a device when a user accesses certain websites. When you interact with Borderfree or its partners, cookies and other technologies may be used for storing information, and accessing information stored on your devices, such as your computer, mobile device or other device. These cookies and other technologies may include first party cookies (i.e., those placed by the website being visited) and third party cookies (i.e., those placed by a website other than the one being visited), Local Shared Objects (commonly referred to as "Flash Cookies" or "HTML 5 Cookies") and tracking pixels (including transparent or clear gifs).

Cookies can either expire at the end of a session ("Session Cookies") or be persistent and last through multiple sessions ("Persistent Cookies"). Session Cookies can be helpful for remembering items you put in your shopping cart as you browse the site, or for security reasons when you are providing financial information. Persistent Cookies are stored on your device in between sessions, which allows for your preferences or actions to be remembered and used on a website (or in some cases across different websites). Persistent Cookies may be helpful in remembering your preferences and choices when using a website or to ensure advertising messages are more relevant to you.

Cookies are useful because they allow us to recognize your device and provide you with a high level of service and relevant offers. If you do not wish to have cookies be used when interacting with Borderfree or its partners, many web browsers allow you to stop accepting cookies and/or to warn you when a third party is trying to transfer a cookie to you. You can take additional steps to disable or delete similar data, such as Flash Cookies, by modifying the "add-on" settings on your browser. You can learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies by [clicking here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118). Various browsers may offer their own management tools for access to HTML5 LSOs. However, please note that certain cookies are required for you to be able to take advantage of some of Borderfree's important functions. For example, if you do not allow our cookies, you may not be able to purchase items from one of our checkouts.

The Borderfree Websites may include Social Media Features, such as the Facebook “Like” button and widgets such as the “Share” button or interactive mini-programs that run on the Borderfree Websites. These Social Media Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social Media Features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on the Borderfree Websites. Your interactions with these Social Media Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing the Social Media Feature.

We partner with third parties to either display advertising on the Borderfree Websites or to manage advertising on other sites. Our third party partners may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on the Borderfree Websites and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests.  If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) (or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

#### How Does Borderfree Use and Share Your Information?

We use and retain your information as needed to provide you services, fulfill your order, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and for other legitimate business reasons. By way of example, and not limitation, we analyze transactional data for the purpose of identifying trends, statistics and measurements that could contribute to the enhancement of Borderfree services. Such use could include identifying market sensitivities, and relative market interest in specific product categories. We may also send you satisfaction questionnaires or other surveys and send you marketing information. Another example would be if you place an order with us through one of our merchant suppliers, we (our merchant supplier or other entity on our behalf) may contact you if there is an issue with the order (e.g., to find an alternative to a restricted item).

We are not in the business of selling your information to others and do not share your information with third parties other than as outlined in this privacy policy. However, there are certain situations where we may provide your information to third parties.

  * Marketplaces and Partners Involved in Your Transactions. Depending on how you interact with Borderfree, you may make purchases that involve third parties. For example, you may make a purchase that involves a third-party website or marketplace. In such situation, you may initially view products on that website or marketplace and Borderfree is facilitating the order or otherwise involved. If this is the case, it will be very clear to you that a third party is involved in your transaction. And, if so, we may share your personal information with that third party.
  * Service Provider. Borderfree may provide your personal information to certain service providers, in connection with the fulfillment of your purchase instructions, including but not limited to delivery agents, email service providers to send you emails on our behalf, customer support providers to process your feedback, customs brokers, international revenue authorities and fraud management parties. Borderfree will always attempt to limit the information we provide to be what is reasonably sufficient for those service providers to carry out their responsibilities as they relate to the fulfillment of your purchase instructions, and to subscribe you to any Borderfree and/or third party marketing messages you opt-in to receive.
  * Opting-In With Third Parties or Use of Third Party Features. If and when you opt-in as described in the Section "How Can You Make Choices About Receiving Marketing, Promotional and Other Information?", we may supply your personal information to third parties. Also, if and when you use third party items that interact with the Borderfree Websites, including third party Social Media Features, third party blogs or other third party applications or items, we may supply your personal information to those third parties.
  * Borderfree's Protection. We will disclose your personal information as required by law, when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process, to enforce or apply our Terms & Conditions and other agreements and to protect the rights of Borderfree.
  * Business Transition. In the event Borderfree goes through a business transition, such as a merger with or acquisition by another company, sale of all or a portion of our assets or brands, your personal information will likely be among the assets transferred.
  * You Otherwise Consent. We may of course share your information in other ways that you specifically consent to.
  * Other Disclosures. We may disclose your personal information to law enforcement, government officials, or other third parties if: (i) we are compelled to do so by subpoena, court order or other legal process, (ii) we must do so to comply with laws, statutes, rules or regulations, including credit card rules, (iii) we believe in good faith that the disclosure is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss, to report suspected illegal activity, or to investigate violations of any rules, regulations, laws or this Privacy Policy.
  * Aggregated Content. We may also share "aggregated/blinded" information with our merchant partners, PR agencies, advertising agencies, and other third parties. By "aggregated/blinded" information we mean, information from multiple users that contains only zip codes, purchasing amounts, products, brands, categories, merchants involved, timing of transactions/usage and frequency of usage – with no other private information or identifying information included.

In addition, in the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, or other similar events, certain information in our possession may be transferred to our successor or assign.

#### How Does Borderfree Handle, Store and Secure Your Information?

We take the security of your data very seriously at Borderfree. We use a variety of current technologies and processes to protect your data, including encryption at both the storage and transport level. However, please note that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

The security of your password is key to the security of your data. We recommend that you do not share, reuse, or store any of your passwords with anyone else.

#### How Can You Make Choices About Receiving Marketing, Promotional and Other Information?

Borderfree may send you marketing, promotional or other information. In certain cases, when interacting with Borderfree, you may be provided with a choice to opt-in or opt-out of receiving such information. In other cases, you will not be presented this choice. If you, at any time, choose to opt-out of receiving such information, we will abide by that marketing preference. Moreover, at any time (no matter what you have chosen or informed us of in the past), you may send us an email at optout@borderfree.com (except that if such preference was made through boxhop.com, please send us an email at optout@boxhop.com) expressing a marketing preference or updating or requesting the deletion of your personal information -- we will abide by that preference and update your personal information accordingly. We will respond to your requests regarding your personal information within 30 days. You may of course also follow the unsubscribe instructions contained in the marketing communications you receive from Borderfree.

In certain cases, we may give you the option to opt-in to receive marketing, promotional or other information from one of our partners or other third party. If you chose to opt-in for that, we will provide your personal information to that third party. BY CHOOSING TO OPT-IN TO A THIRD PARTY, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT ONCE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION HAS BEEN SHARED WITH THAT THIRD PARTY, THE SUBSEQUENT SAFEGUARDING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION WILL BE GOVERNED BY THAT THIRD PARTY’S PRIVACY POLICY, AND ANY REQUEST FOR FURTHER INFORMATION WITH RESPECT TO THEIR INTENDED USE AND/OR TO CHANGE YOUR MARKETING PREFERENCES WITH THAT THIRD PARTY SHALL BE DIRECTED TO THAT THIRD PARTY (AND NOT TO BORDERFREE).

If you have previously opted-in to receive such information from us or a specific third party, declining to opt-in at any future time for us or that third party will not be treated as an opt-out for your marketing preference.

Kindly note that no matter what your marketing preferences are, we may contact you to acknowledge, confirm or fulfill any order that you place, to respond to you or for other legitimate business reasons.

#### What You Should Understand About Third-Party Advertisers and Links to Other Websites?

The Borderfree Websites may include third-party advertising and links to partner websites or other third-party websites. We are not responsible for the content displayed or the practices of any such websites. We recommend that you review the privacy policy and terms and conditions of those websites.

#### Are Children Allowed to Use Borderfree?

Borderfree does not allow anyone under the age of 18 to take part in any of its services. If you are under the age of 18, you must stop using the Borderfree Websites and taking part in its services now. To be clear, but not to limit what you are not allowed to do, if you are under 18, you may not make purchases from Borderfree or any of its partners, you may not click through to any of our partners’ websites, and you may not take part in any surveys, panels or the like.

#### Do We Conduct Questionnaires, Panels, Contests, or Sweepstakes?

We may provide you the opportunity to participate in questionnaires, panels, contests, or sweepstakes. Participation in these questionnaires, panels, contests, or sweepstakes is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose information. We use this information to notify contest winners, award prizes, monitor website traffic, personalize the Borderfree Websites, or for other legitimate business reasons.

We may use a third party service provider to conduct these questionnaires, panels, contests, or sweepstakes. That company is prohibited from using your personal information for any other purpose without your express consent.

#### Has a Third Party Reviewed This Privacy Policy?

We have been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through the Borderfree Websites. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, you should first contact us at safeharbor@borderfree.com or via postal mail at 292 Madison Avenue, 5th Floor, New York, NY 10017. If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint).

#### Is Borderfree Both EU & Swiss Safe Harbor Compliant?

Borderfree complies with the U.S.–E.U. and U.S.–Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal data from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Borderfree has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Borderfree’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor>.

Information submitted by you may be transferred by us to our other offices and/or to the third parties mentioned in the circumstances described above (see How Does Borderfree Use and Share Your Information?), which may be situated (and may be processed by staff operating) in places other than your home jurisdiction, the U.S. and/or the European Economic Area (EEA).  The countries concerned may not have similar data protection laws to your home jurisdiction, the US and the EEA.  Where we transfer your information we will take all reasonable steps to ensure that your privacy continue to be protected.  By submitting information via the Borderfree Website, you agree to this storing, processing and/or transfer.

#### What Should I Know About Changes to This Privacy Policy?

If we decide to change this privacy policy, we will post the updated privacy policy at <http://www.borderfree.com/privacy>[-policy](http://www.borderfree.com/privacy-policy), <http://www.port51.com/privacypolicy> and <http://www.boxhop.com/privacy>. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please come to this link to review it frequently. If we make significantly material changes to this privacy policy, we will notify you by means of a notice on the Borderfree Websites prior to the change becoming effective.

#### What are the Terms & Conditions and Dispute Resolution?

If you choose to visit Borderfree and/or use any of Borderfree's services, your visits and actions, and any disputes over privacy shall be governed exclusively by this privacy policy and the Terms & Conditions at www.borderfree.com/terms, including limitations on liability and exclusive application of the laws of and jurisdiction of the state of New York.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, you should first contact us as provided above. If contacting us does not resolve your complaint, you may raise your complaint with TRUSTe by [Internet here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request), or by fax at 415-520-3420 or mail to TRUSTe Safe Harbor Compliance Dept., [click here](http://www.truste.com/products-and-services/dispute-resolution-services/) for mailing address. If you are faxing or mailing TRUSTe to lodge a complaint, you must include the following information: the name of company, the alleged privacy violation, your contact information, and whether you would like the particulars of your complaint shared with Borderfree. For information about TRUSTe or the operation of TRUSTe's dispute resolution process, [click here](http://www.truste.com/products-and-services/dispute-resolution-services/) or request this information from TRUSTe at any of the addresses listed above. The TRUSTe dispute resolution process shall be conducted in English.
